Jhal
Jhal Jhal
I had taken TCD and number in this, I had
passed some exam and
I got the number in it, so I
wanted to apply in it, but this link is
not opening, friends, it has been four-five days for me
but the link is not opening in this, so
friends,
when will this facility which you are getting not be solved,
this is what I have come to tell you more in this video,
friends, I had
also mailed to CSC that sir, the new
registration is not opening on the link yesterday,
what is the issue, friends, is there a technical issue,
so I had mailed myself, the reply
that came to me was that it will be
rectified by Monday-Tuesday,
friends, right now
it is becoming very difficult to get such things,
friends, but in the coming time,
all this will be rectified, so I will show
you that as we do this new registration,
friends, it is written in
front of us that the field connect to, this is
their link address which is on, this number is
Shringar, that is fine, connection time  Out
please travelator or please try after
sometime, so I am saying that after some time,
try your registration again
or you can do it as many times as you want but this is a
technical issue, friends, whoever has any
website, the
server works on it, which is their posting,
not the one due to which the stress server is correct,
so sometimes the server goes down there,
that you are not able to do this due to some technical issues,
friends, so this is it
and it will be corrected by Monday or Tuesday,
so see friends, once I had
registered in this earlier, then I got an
email, that stay and pain of injection,
friends, 30, this is to
inform you that you left your application to become a bag,
that he has been, right now when Bigg Boss awareness
following region KPO LPO and comment it is
not clear or invalid, this my verification
came, POA means Proof of Identity and
POA means Power of Attorney,
my comment is not clear to them, but
What I saw in my documents was
absolutely clear and correct, so in this, it is becoming
very difficult in today's time to do the
registration,
so how can you do the registration, friends, this
link is going to
open, friends, by Monday or
Tuesday, that is,
your
technical issue on their website will be
fixed, friends, you do
not need to worry, it is present, if you have
spent Rs. 1479 on Joda Sonia and Body,
you have taken 30 numbers, but
now your registration is not happening, then do
not panic, friends,
your registration will start happening on Monday and Tuesday,
or friends, this is all that will happen in this video for today, so
we will
inform you by making a small video through this channel,
friends, if you have come to the channel for the first time, then
subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon so that
you can get the second video on time
and for that, share this video as much as possible
in your WhatsApp group and with
your friends, so come on  Friends, see you
in the next Jio school, till then have a nice time.